kiitosmarimekko.com 2016-03-24

# Privacy Policy | KIITOSlife

Kiitos, Inc./Marimekko respects your personal information and manages it according to the procedures outlined in this Privay Policy. This policy applies solely to information collected by Kiitos, Inc./Marimekko.

Kiitos, Inc./Marimekko is committed to protecting your privacy and uses cautionary measures to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of data used by our system.

We do not rent or sell any of the lists developed through this system. We do not share the lists with any entity outside of Kiitos, Inc./Marimekko.

We collect personal information provided voluntarily during the order process for the sole purpose of fulfilling online shopping orders. Personal information including address, email address and credit card information will be kept strictly confidential.

We may use the contact information we collect to occasionally notify you of online/store promotions or offers we think you'll find valuable. If you do not wish to receive these promotional notices please indicate so by checking the box available during the order process. Each email sent through the system contains an easy way for you to cease receiving email from the sender. If you no longer wish to receive the emails, simply follow the instructions at the end of each email message.

If you wish to update, revise or delete any of the contact information we have collected, please send an email explaining your request to [info@kiitosmarimekko.com](mailto:info@kiitosmarimekko.com).

Although we offer clothing and accessories for children, no area of our site is directed at children under thirteen years of age.

Cookies, or bits of software that track usage, may be sent to your computer. Cookies allow us to track the way our site is being used. Our cookies will never collect specific user information.

If you have any questions about our privacy policy please email them to [info@kiitosmarimekko.com](mailto:info@kiitosmarimekko.com).
